किधर है आदमी दिखाई नहीं दे रहा
हाँ भाई
Hey, what are you doing crazy, you didn't do anything less अरे पागल क्या कर रहे हूँ कुछ कम भी नहीं किया तुमने
Look here look here    इधर देखो इधर देखो
Why didn't work
काम क्यों नहीं किया
Since morning
क्या सुबह से
Don't know what is speaking
क्या बोल्रहे हूँ मालूम नहीं होरहा है
Bread .. why don't you eat bread
रोटी ..क्यों रोटी नहीं खाए
I gave you all the food yesterday
मैंने तू सब खाने का सामान दिया था कल
what is this
ये क्या है
What is this that makes you dirty
ये क्या है पूरा कपडे गंदे करता है तुम
Clean it all
ये देखो सब क्लीन करो
Why don't you work
क्यों काम नहीं करते तुम
Is this work
क्या ये काम है
You have to go to india
तुमको इंडिया जाना है
money...oh
पैसा...पैसा
Tomorrow tomorrow I will give money
कल कल दूंगा पैसा
Come tomorrow come tomorrow
कल आउंगा
My brother is going somewhere, he will come and give you money tomorrow
मेरा भाई कहीं पे जाके है वो आएगा तू कल पैसा दे दूंगा
Hey brother come here
अरे भाई इधर आओ
You don't know arabic
तुम्हे अरबी नहीं मालूम
Does anyone know Arabic here
इधर किसी को भी अरबी मालूम है क्या
What is work
क्या है काम
I do not know what you say
तुम क्या बोलती हूँ मुझे मालूम नहीं हो रहा है
Ok ok i am going to pakistani return
ओके ठीक है में पाकिस्तानी के पास जाके अत हूँ
hey brother
hey pakistani
hey pakistani come here
Assalam waliyakum
अस्सलाम वलियकुम
walaikum salam
how are you fine...
कैसे हूँ ठीक हूँ......
repeat dailuge.....
What are you doing
क्या काम कर रहे हूँ
repeat dailuge.....
What is it all about
ये क्या सब वैसा क्या वैसा पड़ा है
repeat dailuge.....
all repeat repeat dailuge